All right, this is the video we have been waiting for.
这将是我们一直期待的视频内容
We are going to learn how to ask the user for permission
我们将学习如何向用户请求
to view their location and to track their location.
位置信息查看和跟踪权限
What we'll do is inside of askPermission down here,
我们转到 askPermission 中
let's go ahead and fill this out.
补充完整所需的代码
What we want to do is we will say permissions.askAsync.
输入 Permissions.askAsync
So instead of get async, it's askAsync.
这里是 askAsync 而不是 getAsync
What we are asking for,
我们要请求的权限
just as we are on line 15, is saying permissions.location.
和第 15 行的一样 即 permissions.LOCATION
Then, what's going to happen is we are going to get
然后就像在 componentDidMount 中一样
a status back just like we did and component did mount.
我们将获得一个 status
And then now what we can say is if the status is granted,
如果 status 为 granted
then what we want to do is let's go ahead and say return it's called setlocation.
则 return this.setLocation
If it's not granted,
如果未授予权限
then just as we did before,
则像之前一样
we'll just set the status so that our state is aware of what's happening.
设置 status 使状态知道所发生的情况
And then any error we get,
如果出现任何错误
let's just go ahead and make sure that we log that so we are aware of it.
确保记录错误 以便知晓这些错误
Say console.warn, let's just say error asking location permission,
输入 console.warn 输出消息“error asking Location permission:”
and then we will log the error.
然后输出错误日志
All right. That looks good. I did notice one typo here.
看起来不错 发现这里有个拼写错误
This should be askAsync.
这里应该是 askAsync
You probably saw that but I obviously did not.
你之前可能已经发现了 明显我没有发现
So now what's going to happen,
我们转到应用界面
let's see this in action.
看看实际运行效果
We go to live.
转到 Live
You notice, hey you need to enable location services for this app.
系统提示“You need to enable location services for this app.”
When we click on enable,
当我们点击 Enable 时
notice we get this sweet little pop up here saying,
弹出了一条消息
expo would like to have access to your location.
提示 expo 想要访问你的位置信息
Do you want to allow it or deny it?
允许还是拒绝？
I'm going to go ahead and click allow,
我将点击“Allow”
and then you'll notice we have some information here,
然后出现了一些信息
but this is the information from
但这些信息是静态信息
the static data not the data we're getting from the phone.
并非从手机中获取的信息
So what I want to do real quick is update our render methods.
我将快速更新下 render 方法
You'll notice that we still have direction and coordinates down here.
这里依然包含 direction 和 coords
So here instead of saying North,
将这里的 North
what we want to stay is direction.
改为 direction
And here instead of just logging or showing 200,
这里不再直接显示 200
what we want to say is let's say math.round(coords.altitude),
而是改为 Math.round(coords.altitude)
and then what we're going to do is we are going to times that by
然后乘以 3.2808
3.2808 in order to convert that in to feet.
以便转换为英尺
And then same thing with miles per hour,
每小时英里数也一样
what we will do is coords.speed times 2.2369,
输入 coords.speed * 2.2369
I believe if I remember my physics classes.
我觉得我的物理知识应该没记错
And then what we're going to say is.tofixed(1),
然后输入 .toFixed(1)
and that's going to convert it into miles per hour.
将会转换为英里/小时
So let's go ahead and see if this works.
看看是否可行
All right there we go. You'll notice here that
你会发现
my simulator is changing the miles per hour.
我的模拟器在不断更改 MPH 值
The way you can do that is if you go to hardware and then you go over to debug,
转到 Hardware 然后转到 Debug
head down to location and notice you can select your location here.
转到 Location 在这里可以选择位置信息模式
So I'm doing a city bicycle ride because I'm going roughly at 60 miles an hour.
我的是骑行状态 因为速度大约为 60 英里/小时
Notice if I went on a freeway drive,
如果选择 Freeway Drive
what's going to happen is my speed should eventually increase.
我的速度最终会增大
What's also cool about this too is,
另一个比较酷的地方是
there it goes and it changes directions as well.
还会更改方向